<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meowpedia</string>

    <string name="cat_type">Jenis Kucing</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
    <string name="name_profile">Nabiila Widya Khoirunissa</string>
    <string name="email_profile">nabiilawidya7702@gmail.com</string>

    <string-array name="data_cat">
        <item>Persian Cat</item>
        <item>Siamese Cat</item>
        <item>Maine Coon</item>
        <item>Bengal Cat</item>
        <item>Scottish Fold</item>
        <item>Ragdoll Cat</item>
        <item>Sphynx Cat</item>
        <item>British Shorthair</item>
        <item>Abyssinian Cat</item>
        <item>Exotic Shorthair</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>Known for their long, luxurious fur and sweet temperament, Persian cats are one of the most popular breeds worldwide.\n
            Persian cats, with their regal appearance and serene demeanor, have captivated cat lovers for centuries. Their expressive eyes and gentle disposition make them cherished companions in homes around the world. Despite their glamorous coats requiring regular grooming, Persian cats are known for their easygoing nature and adaptability to indoor living. They enjoy lounging in sunlit spots and appreciate quiet moments of affection from their owners. With their charming personalities and undeniable elegance, Persian cats continue to hold a special place in the hearts of cat enthusiasts everywhere.
        </item>
        <item>Characterized by their striking blue almond-shaped eyes and sleek, slender bodies, Siamese cats are known for their vocal and social nature.\m
            Siamese cats, often dubbed the "royalty of the feline world," possess a rich history and distinctive personality traits that set them apart. Their enchanting blue eyes seem to penetrate the soul, adding to their mystique. Beyond their physical allure, Siamese cats are renowned for their intelligence and love for human interaction. They are not only vocal but also highly communicative, often engaging their owners in lively conversations. Their playful and outgoing nature makes them ideal companions for those seeking an interactive and affectionate feline friend. Siamese cats thrive on attention and are known to form strong bonds with their families, displaying unwavering loyalty and devotion.</item>
        <item>Recognized for their large size, tufted ears, and bushy tails, Maine Coons are affectionate and playful cats that are often referred to as "gentle giants."\n
            Maine Coon cats, with their majestic presence and endearing characteristics, hold a special place in the hearts of cat enthusiasts worldwide. Beyond their impressive size and distinctive physical features, such as tufted ears and bushy tails, Maine Coons are celebrated for their gentle and amiable nature. Despite their imposing stature, these gentle giants possess a remarkably sweet temperament, often displaying affectionate and sociable behavior towards both humans and other pets. Renowned for their playful antics and remarkable intelligence, Maine Coons thrive on mental and physical stimulation, enjoying interactive games and puzzles that challenge their agile minds. Their laid-back demeanor and adaptable nature make them beloved members of households, where they eagerly participate in family activities and provide companionship that enriches the lives of their owners. Whether lounging in a sunny spot or engaging in playful romps, Maine Coon cats exude charm and grace, embodying the epitome of feline majesty.</item>
        <item>With their distinctive leopard-like spots and sleek coats, Bengal cats are energetic and intelligent companions that enjoy interactive playBengal cats, with their wild and captivating appearance, evoke the spirit of the jungle within the confines of the home. Beyond their striking leopard-like spots and sleek coats, Bengal cats possess a spirited and inquisitive nature that sets them apart. Their boundless energy and innate curiosity drive them to explore their surroundings with enthusiasm, often engaging in playful antics that entertain and amuse their human companions. Renowned for their intelligence and problem-solving abilities, Bengal cats thrive on mental stimulation and interactive play, eagerly participating in games that challenge their agile minds and nimble bodies. Despite their wild appearance, Bengal cats form strong bonds with their owners, displaying affectionate and loyal behavior that underscores their status as cherished companions. Whether leaping gracefully through the air or curling up in a cozy lap, Bengal cats exude charm and charisma, captivating the hearts of all who encounter them.</item>
        <item>Named for their unique folded ears, Scottish Folds have a sweet and gentle disposition, making them popular pets worldwide.\n
            Scottish Fold cats, with their adorable folded ears and endearing expression, are beloved for more than just their distinctive appearance. Their sweet and gentle disposition is a hallmark of the breed, making them sought-after companions in homes around the globe. Beyond their physical charm, Scottish Folds are known for their affectionate nature and amiable temperament. They delight in curling up in the laps of their owners, purring contentedly as they bask in the warmth of companionship. Despite their laid-back demeanor, Scottish Folds possess a playful streak, enjoying interactive toys and games that engage their curiosity and keep them entertained. Their adaptable nature makes them well-suited to various living environments, from bustling households to serene apartments. With their irresistible charm and unwavering devotion, Scottish Folds have rightfully earned their place as cherished members of the family, bringing joy and comfort to all who have the pleasure of welcoming them into their lives.</item>
        <item>Known for their affectionate nature and tendency to go limp when picked up, Ragdoll cats are lar.\n
            Ragdoll cats, often described as "puppy-like" due to their affectionate and social demeanor, are adored for more than just their propensity to go limp when held. These gentle giants boast a combination of beauty, grace, and charm that captivates cat lovers worldwide. With their large, fluffy bodies and soft, plush fur, Ragdolls exude an irresistible allure that invites cuddles and affection. Renowned for their docile and laid-back nature, Ragdoll cats are often found nestled in the arms of their owners, eagerly seeking out warmth and companionship. Their easygoing temperament makes them ideal companions for families and individuals alike, as they thrive on attention and affection. Despite their tranquil demeanor, Ragdolls are not devoid of playfulness, delighting in interactive toys and games that stimulate their agile minds and bodies. Whether lounging lazily in a sunbeam or frolicking with their favorite toys, Ragdoll cats epitomize the perfect balance of beauty, grace, and affection, bringing joy and comfort to all who have the privilege of sharing their lives with them.</item>
        <item>Recognizable by their hairless bodies and large ears, Sphynx cats are lively and affectionate companions that require regular grooming to maintain their skin health.\n
            Sphynx cats, with their unique appearance and playful personality, defy conventional notions of feline beauty. Despite their hairless bodies, Sphynx cats possess an undeniable charm and charisma that captivates all who encounter them. Beyond their distinctive physical features, Sphynx cats are renowned for their outgoing and affectionate nature. They thrive on human interaction and are often found nestled in the laps of their owners, seeking warmth and companionship. Their lively demeanor and boundless energy make them delightful companions for families and individuals seeking an engaging pet. Despite their lack of fur, Sphynx cats require regular grooming to maintain their skin health, including baths to remove excess oils and debris. Despite this grooming requirement, Sphynx cats eagerly participate in grooming sessions, enjoying the attention and affection bestowed upon them by their owners. With their endearing personality and unique appearance, Sphynx cats bring joy and companionship to households around the world, proving that beauty truly does lie beyond the surface.</item>
        <item>With their round faces and dense, plush coats, British Shorthairs are calm and easygoing cats that make excellent family pets.\n
            British Shorthair cats, with their charming round faces and plush coats that exude an air of sophistication, have endeared themselves to cat lovers for generations. Beyond their physical attributes, British Shorthairs are known for their calm and composed demeanor, making them ideal companions for families seeking a laid-back pet. Their easygoing nature allows them to adapt well to various living environments, from bustling households to tranquil apartments. Despite their serene disposition, British Shorthairs are not devoid of playfulness, enjoying interactive toys and games that engage their curiosity and stimulate their minds. They form strong bonds with their human companions and are often found lounging nearby, offering quiet companionship and affectionate gestures. With their gentle temperament and unwavering loyalty, British Shorthair cats truly embody the essence of a beloved family pet, bringing joy and comfort to all who have the pleasure of sharing their lives with them.</item>
        <item>Known for their sleek, muscular build and distinctive "ticked" coat pattern, Abyssinian cats are active, intelligent, and love to explore their surroundings.\n
            Abyssinian cats, with their exotic appearance and adventurous spirit, are captivating companions that leave a lasting impression on all who encounter them. Beyond their sleek and muscular build, Abyssinians are celebrated for their intelligence and inquisitive nature. They possess a keen intellect and insatiable curiosity, eagerly exploring every nook and cranny of their environment with boundless energy and enthusiasm. Their athletic prowess and agility enable them to excel in various activities, from climbing to jumping, making them adept adventurers both indoors and outdoors. Despite their active lifestyle, Abyssinian cats form deep bonds with their human companions, seeking out affection and companionship with unwavering loyalty. Their distinctive "ticked" coat pattern adds to their allure, showcasing their individuality and beauty. With their dynamic personality and striking appearance, Abyssinian cats enrich the lives of those fortunate enough to call them family, embodying the essence of the perfect feline companion.</item>
        <item>Similar in appearance to Persian cats but with shorter coats, Exotic Shorthairs are affectionate and laid-back companions that are easy to groom and care for.\n
            Exotic Shorthair cats, with their adorable flattened faces and plush coats, epitomize the perfect blend of charm and simplicity. While they bear a striking resemblance to Persian cats, their shorter coats make them easier to groom and care for, making them an ideal choice for busy households. Beyond their low-maintenance grooming requirements, Exotic Shorthairs are beloved for their affectionate and laid-back nature. They thrive on companionship and are often found lounging nearby, ready to offer quiet affection and companionship to their human family members. Despite their calm demeanor, Exotic Shorthairs possess a playful streak, enjoying interactive toys and games that engage their curiosity and stimulate their minds. Their adaptable nature makes them well-suited to various living environments, from bustling apartments to serene households. With their gentle disposition and undeniable charm, Exotic Shorthair cats bring joy and comfort to all who have the pleasure of welcoming them into their homes, embodying the essence of the perfect feline companion.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_picture">
        <item>@drawable/persia</item>
        <item>@drawable/siamese</item>
        <item>@drawable/mainecoon</item>
        <item>@drawable/bengal</item>
        <item>@drawable/scottishfold</item>
        <item>@drawable/ragdoll</item>
        <item>@drawable/sphynx</item>
        <item>@drawable/britishshorthair</item>
        <item>@drawable/abyssinians</item>
        <item>@drawable/exoticshorthair</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>